You should have changed the TextView into a ListView element.
Then you can remove this text attribute because you don't need it anymore.
Now from the UX mocks, you'll remember that the list takes up the whole screen,
so we want to set the width and height to be match_parent. That will make
the ListView match the dimensions of its parent, which is this RelativeLayout.
And to find out the parent of this RelativeLayout, it's actually in this
activity_main XML file because the fragment is contained within the activity.
Within this file, we see that this view is also match_parent for height and
width. So now we can confirm that the ListView actually will take up
the full screen. Going back to the fragment_main file, we can add the id,
listview_forecast, onto the ListView. And then, since this layout only contains
one child, we can simplify the layout by changing this into a FrameLayout.